tutorialgateway.org 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how TutorialGateway.org collects, uses, maintains and discloses the personal information collected from every individual user of [www.tutorialgateway.org](https://www.tutorialgateway.org/) website.

### Information we collection

TutorialGateway.org may collect personal information from Users in various ways including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, filling the contact form, subscribe to the newsletter, sending emails and using the services, features available in this site. When filling the form, Users may be asked to enter an appropriate name and email address. We may also collect the personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submitted to us. Users have every right to refuse to supply personal information, however, it may prevent them from accessing certain services (but not all) provided by the site.

### How do we use the Collected Information?

Tutorialgateway.org may use the information obtained by cookies, log files, device identifiers and location data in one of the following ways:

  *  **To provide better User Experience:** We may use the user’s information to personalize the page as per the individual needs.
  *  **To improve our Website:** We may use the user’s feedback to improve the look and design of our website.
  *  **For providing Better Service:** We might use the user’s information to respond to the queries or provide service personally or individually.
  *  **To provide Information:** We may use the user’s Email address to send occasional emails about the important updates, site changes and newly added services.
  *  **To send Periodical Emails:** If the user subscribes to our website then we will use his Email address to send the information about posts regularly. Every user has right to Unsubscribe this services at any point of time by clicking unsubscribe link at the bottom of every Email.

### How we protect your information

We implement appropriate storage and processing practices and security measures to protect the data collected by this website against unauthorized access, data alteration or disclosure of your personal information such as username, password, email information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing of Your Information

We will not share, trade, rent or sell your personal information to others without your approval, except as mentioned below:

  * TutorialGateway.org will disclose your personal information if it is required by the law, or ordered by the law, or to protect our rights or others, or to protect the personal safety of this site, and the Users of this site.
  * We may share the Users Demographic information with our business partners, trusted Advertisers and Affiliates. This will not include any personal information that can identify the individual person.
  * We may share certain information, including Browser name, Platform, Hardware information, system information obtained by cookies, log files, device identifiers and location data with our third party business partners to deliver the quality Service.

### Third Party Websites

We are not responsible for the content and policy practices of the websites linked from our site or to this site. Occasionally, we may refer to third party websites (URLs) to provide the information on the topics we haven’t covered. Please remember, every website may have its own privacy policies. So, when you use the links from tutorialgateway.org to a third-party website, you are no longer subjected to our Privacy Policies. We strongly recommend the users to check, Third party websites Privacy Policies before browsing them.

### Your Consent

By using this site you are agreed with us, to collect and use your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policies in future, We will update this page to keep you aware of the changes we made. We strongly recommend the users to frequently check this page, to understand the changes we made to our Privacy Policies.

### Contacting Us

If you have any queries about our Privacy Policy, Please feel free to contact us at:

[[email protected]](https://www.tutorialgateway.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4322272e2a2d033736372c312a222f2422372634223a6d2c3124)

This Privacy Policy was last modified on July 26, 2017
